Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Group photo of men at the school. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref785)
  Color Photography; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints
- Group photo of school staff. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref786)
  Teachers; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Girls singing during a school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref787)
  Children; Uniforms; Choirs; Color Photography; Students; Singing/Singers; Girls; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- School staff. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref788)
  Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Facial Hair
- Boys singing during a school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref789)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Choirs; Singing/Singers; Children; Uniforms; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Boys; Group Portraits
- Students carrying school flags in a school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref790)
  Uniforms; Parades/Processions; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Schools/Education; Flags; Students; Marching Band; Boys; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Events/Occasions; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Boy scouts holding flags. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref791)
  Marching Band; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Scouts; Children; Flags; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits
- Students marching and carrying flags in the city. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref792)
  Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Students; Photographic Prints; Men; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Buildings; Flags; Streets/Roads; Children; Color Photography; Parades/Processions; Police; Group Portraits
- Boy scouts marching with flags. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref793)
  Outdoors; Flags; Streets/Roads; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Scouts; Parades/Processions; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Buildings; Group Portraits
- School's taekwondo team marching in the street.10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref794)
  Sports; Students; Boys; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Men; Schools/Education; Teachers; Outdoors; Cars/Trucks; Color Photography; Police; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Parades/Processions; Transportation; Group Portraits
- Marching band. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref795)
  Men; Parades/Processions; Brass Instruments; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Flags; Outdoors; Buildings; Uniforms; Streets/Roads; Musical Instruments; Helwan, Egypt; Marching Band; Facial Hair
- Girls marching with trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref796)
  Color Photography; Children; Parades/Processions; Men; Outdoors; Flags; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Uniforms; Students; Photographic Prints; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Awards
- Boys marching with flags and trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref797)
  Flags; Buses; Students; Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Boys; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Parades/Processions; Street Lamps; Children; Transportation; Awards; Group Portraits
- Students marching in the street. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref798)
  Outdoors; Architecture; Children; Buildings; Boys; Parades/Processions; Girls; Color Photography; Students; Streets/Roads; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Men
- Boys marching in the street. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref799)
  Uniforms; Color Photography; Parades/Processions; Streets/Roads; Students; Outdoors; Buildings; Men; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits
- Boys marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref800)
  Arabic Writing; Uniforms; Outdoors; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Men; Boys; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Parades/Processions; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Teachers; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits
- Students marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref801)
  Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Girls; Students; Men; Boys; Outdoors; Streets/Roads; Awards; Uniforms; Flags; Schools/Education; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Parades/Processions; Kiosks/Kushk; Street Lamps; Group Portraits
- Boys marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref802)
  Boys; Men; Students; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Parades/Processions; Outdoors; Streets/Roads; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers
- Students marching in the streets celebrating the 100th anniversary of Holy Family School. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref803)
  Transportation; Parades/Processions; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Buses; Boys; Girls; Cars/Trucks; Schools/Education; Men; Cameras; Buildings; Women; Streets/Roads; Students; Uniforms; Religious Sites; Children; Group Portraits
- Man speaking in front of students. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref804)
  Uniforms; Uniforms; Men; Scouts; Children; Parades/Processions; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Outdoors; Boys; Flags; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait of the taekwondo team. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref805)
  Schools/Education; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Students; Boys; Sports; Uniforms; Children; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of students wearing sashes. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref806)
  Students; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Boys; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Children; Outdoors; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt
- Taekwondo team performing in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref807)
  Children; Uniforms; Boys; Outdoors; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Crowds; Sports; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Students; Men; Group Portraits
- Group portrait of men and nuns.10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref808)
  Photographic Prints; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Nuns; Group Portraits; Men; Schools/Education; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Group of men smiling. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref809)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Facial Hair
- Boy scouts performing in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref810)
  Scouts; Uniforms; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Crowds; Tents; Audiences/Spectators; Boys; Students; Group Portraits
- A man speaking into a microphone standing next to a table of trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref811)
  Schools/Education; Women; Awards; Men; Scouts; Speeches; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Helwan, Egypt; Microphones; Musical Instruments; Individual Portraits
- Boy scouts demonstrating their skills in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref812)
  Scouts; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Color Photography; Students; Nuns; Children; Audiences/Spectators; Group Portraits
- Girls choir singing on stage. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref813)
  Nuns; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Musical Instruments; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Students; Singing/Singers; Children; Girls; Uniforms; Group Portraits
- A group portrait of students wearing sashes. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref814)
  Schools/Education; Color Photography; Students; Boys; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Events/Occasions
- Man speaking with a microphone. 10.1 x 15.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref815)
  Speeches; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Awards; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Men; Microphones; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Individual Portraits
- The audience at a school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref816)
  Teachers; Color Photography; Students; Priests/Clergymen; Crowds; Schools/Education; Audiences/Spectators; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Women; Boys; Girls; Children; Group Portraits
- The audience at a school awards ceremony. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref817)
  Children; Buildings; Audiences/Spectators; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Awards; Boys; Girls; Students; Teachers; Men; Group Portraits
- A camera man in front of the audience at a school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref818)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Cameras; Men; Women; Students; Audiences/Spectators; Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Children
- Crowd at school event from above. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref819)
  Students; Outdoors; Audiences/Spectators; Cameras; Teachers; Women; Men; Girls; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits
- Men standing behind a table of trophies. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref820)
  Teachers; Speeches; Microphones; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Awards; Schools/Education; Men; Cameras; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits
- Men presenting awards. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref821)
  Ceremonies; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Men; Women; Awards; Cameras; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits
- Man awarding students with medals. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref822)
  Helwan, Egypt; Awards; Medals/Insignia; Ceremonies; Men; Schools/Education; Children; Students; Boys; Musical Instruments; Teachers; Color Photography; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- Man awarding a nun with a trophy. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref823)
  Men; Women; Awards; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Musical Instruments; Nuns; Ceremonies; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits
- Girls dancing at a school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref824)
  Girls; Performing Arts; Crowds; Musical Instruments; Students; Schools/Education; Men; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Women; Photographic Prints; Children; Color Photography; Dancing; Audiences/Spectators; Group Portraits
- Girls holding balloons during school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref825)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Balloons; Color Photography; Children; Schools/Education; Cameras; Teachers; Men; Students; Girls; Women; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions
- Girls dancing at a school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref826)
  Schools/Education; Color Photography; Musical Instruments; Women; Crowds; Performance Plays; Men; Students; Girls; Children; Dancing; Audiences/Spectators; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits
- Girls dancing at school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref827)
  Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Performing Arts; Awards; Crowds; Girls; Dancing; Costumes; Children; Group Portraits
- Men eating. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref828)
  Teachers; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Drinks/Beverages; Food; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Advertisements
- Men eating. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref829)
  Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Food; Schools/Education; Teachers; Men; Group Portraits
- Group portrait. 14.9 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref830)
  Uniforms; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Group Portraits; Police; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A clergyman with with two boys. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref831)
  Children; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Bow Ties; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Boys; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Group portrait in front of Egyptian flag. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref832)
  Flags; Color Photography; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Men; Teachers; Police; Boys; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Children; Group Portraits
- A clergyman shaking hands with a boy. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref833)
  Boys; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Medals/Insignia; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Children; Color Photography; Students; Schools/Education; Group Portraits
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref834)
  Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Boys; Women; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- The audience at a school event. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref835)
  Photographic Prints; Children; Boys; Girls; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Men; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Audiences/Spectators; Facial Hair
- Award ceremony. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref836)
  Children; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Medals/Insignia; Color Photography; Teachers; Awards; Boys; Students; Men; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- A teacher receiving an award during an honoring ceremony. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref837)
  Students; Color Photography; Boys; Men; Schools/Education; Awards; Women; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Ceremonies; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A student receiving an award in an honoring ceremony. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref838)
  Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Men; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Awards; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- Students carrying flags during a school event.12.9 x 8.8 cm, 1982 (Object AD_MC_028_ref839)
  Parades/Processions; Children; Boys; Arabic Writing; Men; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Students; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- Children performing in a school event.12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref840)
  Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Men; Musical Instruments; Microphones; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Performing Arts; Events/Occasions
- Student posing with his trophy at a school event. 8.8 x 12.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref842)
  Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Awards; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Children
- Photo of a teacher shaking hands with a police officer. 10.1 x 15.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref843)
  Officials; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Microphones; Cigarettes; Uniforms; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Men; Police; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- A police officer eating with teachers in school. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref844)
  Schools/Education; Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Drinks/Beverages; Color Photography; Police; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Food; Women; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits
- A teacher receiving an award during a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref845)
  Color Photography; Schools/Education; Teachers; Awards; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits
- Teacher receiving an award in a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref846)
  Photographic Prints; Awards; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Women; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Group Portraits
- School staff with a police officer. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref847)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Color Photography; Men; Officials; Police; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- School staff in an office. 14.9 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref848)
  Women; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Offices; Schools/Education; Awards; Group Portraits
- Boy scouts with the scoutmaster. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref849)
  Group Portraits; Uniforms; Men; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Photographic Prints; Scouts; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Students singing at a school event. 12.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref850)
  Uniforms; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Musical Instruments; Singing/Singers; Choirs; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Boys; Men; Facial Hair; Microphones; Group Portraits
- Student receiving an award in an honoring ceremony. 13.6 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref851)
  Teachers; Women; Schools/Education; Awards; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group photo of the school's clergymen. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref852)
  Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Student receiving an award in an honoring ceremony in school. 12.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref853)
  Color Photography; Schools/Education; Boys; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Women; Awards; Medals/Insignia; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- A woman taking a photograph at a school event. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref854)
  Schools/Education; Head Covers/Veils; Cameras; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Women; Color Photography; Boys; Students; Children; Individual Portraits; Hats
- Group photo of school staff at a school event.12.3 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref855)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Microphones; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Men; Teachers; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group photo of school staff. 12 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref856)
  Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School staff with two saluting policemen. 13.1 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref857)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Police; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Awards; Men; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Student receiving an award from a policeman. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref858)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Women; Boys; Students; Awards; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Police; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Ceremonies; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students performing in a school event. 13.1 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref859)
  Men; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Percussion Instruments; Children; Singing/Singers; Uniforms; Boys; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School staff poside behind a table of trophies. 13.2 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref860)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Awards; Women; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Teachers receiving awards in an honoring ceremony. 11.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref861)
  Men; Cigarettes; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Military/Soldiers; Police; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Awards; Schools/Education; Women; Teachers; Medals/Insignia; Smoking; Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits
- Group photo of school staff. 13.1 x 8.9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref862)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Teachers; Women; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A man and a policeman with two students. 12.4 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref863)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Officials; Children; Awards; Schools/Education; Police; Men; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Teachers; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Singer performing in a school event. 9 x 12.5 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref864)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Microphones; Boys; Men; Singing/Singers; Oud; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children
- Group photo of school staff with an official. 13.3 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref865)
  Teachers; Drinks/Beverages; Helwan, Egypt; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Officials; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Men; Food; Police; Group Portraits; Medals/Insignia; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group photo of school staff with a student. 13.1 x 8.7 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref866)
  Boys; Teachers; Students; Men; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School staff in a school event. 13.8 x 9 cm, 1 December 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref867)
  Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt
- Children performing in a school event. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref868)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Singing/Singers; Schools/Education; Boys; Color Photography; Teachers; Microphones; Students; Children; Radios; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits
- Group photo of teachers. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref869)
  Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Teachers eating. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref870)
  Head Covers/Veils; Arabic Writing; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Teachers; Food; Group Portraits
- A scoutmaster with a group of boy scouts behind him. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref871)
  Scouts; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Schools/Education; Boys; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Children; Photographic Prints; Scouts; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- Group school photo. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref872)
  Color Photography; Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Group photo of school staff. 12.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref873)